igpmanager.com 2019-03-27

# Privacy Policy

iGP Games means iGP Games Limited (hereinafter referred to as "us," "we," or "iGP Games") are committed to respecting the privacy rights of the customers, visitors, and other users of iGP Games' computer game iGP Manager (the "Game") and its related website igpmanager.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy (" **Policy** ") explains how we use and protect the information that we handle. Please read this Policy carefully as it will apply each time you submit information or data to the Game or Site and you agree that we may use that data and information in accordance with this Policy. 

Here are the details that the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regards to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, known as General Data Protection Regulation ( **GDPR** ) says we have to give you as a 'data controller': 

  * Our Site address is [https://igpmanager.com](https://igpmanager.com/)
  * Our company name is iGP Games Limited 
  * Our registered address is at Third Floor, 207 Regent Street, London, W1B 3HH 
  * If you have any comments or questions on this Policy, please email them to [contact@igpmanager.com](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com)

## I. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES

###  A. What are the lawful basis for processing of personal data? 

Under GDPR we will ensure that your personal data is processed lawfully, fairly, and transparently, without adversely affecting your rights. We will only process your personal data if at least one of the following basis applies: 

  1. you have given consent to the processing of your personal data for one or more specific purposes; 
  2. processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or in order to take steps at the request of you prior to entering into a contract; 
  3. processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject; 
  4. processing is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or of another natural person; 
  5. processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller; and/or 
  6. processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party such as our credit card payment processing, except where such interests are overridden by the fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data. 

###  B. What Basic Information Does iGP Games Collect? 

We only collect personal data from you on a voluntary basis, and you may visit areas on the Site without providing us with such. However, in order to use certain parts of the Site and/or log-on to play the Game, you will be required to create an account by providing us your email address and selecting a unique username, or a name, surname and password (an "Account"). For age verification purposes, we may also ask for your birth date. You may also use your photo for your Account and we will ask for your consent to use that photo for the purpose of your Account. 

In the course of maintaining your Account, you might also be asked to participate in online surveys about the Game, or in other Game-related promotional contests, participation in which is entirely voluntary and we will ask your consent in order to process your personal data in that way. You might also desire to contact our customer support team via the Forum or the "Contact Us" link found on the Site. You might be requested to provide additional information beyond your email address, including your name, birthday, and other contact information so that we can provide support as is necessary for the provision of our services to you, or, if not necessary, on the basis of your consent. Where a current user uses our "refer-a-friend" scheme, we will not be exposed to or process any personal data about potential users until those potential users register to play our Game/ use our services. 

We may contact you by email in relation to products and services that we offer only where you give us consent to contact you in that way. You may unsubscribe at any time by following the link in our emails or by contacting us at [contact@igpmanager.com](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com). 

Please note that in utilising certain areas of the Site (e.g. purchasing merchandise) or the Game you will be requested to provide additional information in order to complete a purchase, such as your name, address and credit card or other payment information. This information will be collected by or provided to the third-party payment provider, and none of this information is stored by iGP Games. Please see Section IV below regarding how third-parties working on behalf of iGP Games use your personal information. 

The Game offers certain optional in-app purchases, such as additional "tokens" that can be purchased in the "shop" if you choose to do so. You will need to confirm by pressing "Yes/Okay" before you can visit the shop. Certain third parties, such as Google or Apple, will ask you to confirm your choice of additional items before the purchase. Any payments for the in-app purchases are processed by third party providers including Stripe and PayPal. 

###  C. What Additional Information Does iGP Games Collect? 

  1. **AUTOMATIC COLLECTION**. Our servers automatically recognise visitors' domain names and internet protocol (IP) addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). In addition, your web browser or Game software may transmit to iGP Games certain geographic information or other information regarding your computer, including its capabilities, hardware specs and game data processing. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous "traffic data" that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. 
  2. **COOKIES**. We use the standard "cookies" feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to the Site. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies, nor do we employ any data capture mechanisms on the Site other than cookies. We use cookies primarily to confirm when you are logged into the Game. We may also use cookies help us learn which areas of the Site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at the Site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended. 

###  D. What Does iGP Games Do With Collected Information? 

  1. **PERSONAL INFORMATION**. We will not share your personal information with any third-parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We may use your personal information to verify your identity or to check your qualifications, to inform you of any changes to the Site or Game. We may also use your information to contact you should we believe that you are in violation of the Terms of Service Agreement ("Terms of Service") or the End User License Agreement ("EULA"). At your discretion, you may choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers that are not associated with iGP Games through on-site offers. We will not provide your information to them without your consent. In addition, we may use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, to administer the Site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate basis. 
  2. **ANONYMOUS INFORMATION**. We use anonymous information to analyse the Site traffic, but we do not examine this information for individually identifying information. 
  3. **USE OF COOKIES**. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site, or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on the Site by third party advertisers may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on the Site and you should check the relevant third partyâ€™s cookies policy, including any cookies preferences they might offer you. You may also be able to control cookies preferences within your browser settings. 
  4. **DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on iGP Games subsidiaries or affiliates, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of iGP Games or the users of the Site or Game, or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site or Game. 
  5. **SALE OF INFORMATION**. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through the Site or otherwise collected in connection with the Game. If iGP Games or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquiring party/parties. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you, either through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site. 
  6. **ACCESS TO INFORMATION**. You may access your personal data or request changes to the information that we collect and hold about you 

###  E. Notice Concerning Children 

PLEASE NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online, and as such do not knowingly collect any personal information from any user under age 13. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site or Game user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user's Account. 

###  F. What are my rights in relation to personal data? 

Under the GDPR, you have the right to: 

  * request access to, deletion of or correction of, your personal data held by us at no cost to you; 
  * request that your personal data be transferred to another person (data portability); 
  * be informed of what data processing is taking place; 
    * restrict processing; 
  * to object to processing of your personal data; and 
    * complain to a supervisory authority. 

You also have rights with respect to automated decision-making and profiling as set out below. 

To enforce any of the foregoing rights or if you have any other questions about our site or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [Support Team](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com)

## II. SECURITY

We store your personal data in a database hosted within the EEA. It may be processed outside the EEA as may be necessary for the provision of our services and deal with payments. By giving us your personal data you agree to this arrangement. We will do what we reasonably can to keep your data secure. 

We will keep your Account data for as long as you are using our services, subject to availability, and will delete the Account with your data 10 years after your last log-in, unless we are required to keep it for legal reasons. 

The Site and the Game have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you. We store your personal information on secured servers in secured facilities with restricted access, protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to iGP Games employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the Site and the Game. All iGP Games personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. 

We use additional security measures to enhance security, such as analysing account behaviour for fraudulent or otherwise anomalous behaviour, may limit use of site features in response to possible signs of abuse, may remove inappropriate content or links to illegal content, and may suspend or disable accounts for violations of our Terms of Service. 

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your information, please be aware that no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through the use of the Game or the Site and we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss or misuse to you or to any third-party. You acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software. 

Should you have any concern or knowledge of security violations please report them to the [Support Team](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com). 

## III. WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND OUR CONTROL

###  A. Public Forums and In-Game Chat Text 

The Site includes a section for interactive "forums" in the form of message boards (the "Forums") to which users with an Account and an in-Game name may post. Additionally, within the Game, you can participate in real-time interactive chat ("Chat") with other players. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in the Forums or Chat becomes public information in which you relinquish any expectation of privacy. Remember that iGP Games asks that you not disclose any personal information when posting in the Forums or in Chat, and you should exercise caution when deciding what information to share. We reserve the right, but shall have no obligation, to monitor your use of the Forums or Chat. 

###  B. Third-Party Websites 

The Site may contain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies. 

## IV. SERVICE PROVIDERS

We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf, such as to fulfil product orders, collect billing information and process payments. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. Any financial information submitted, however, such as your credit card information and billing address, is provided solely to the third-party payment provider, and none of this information is collected by, shared with, or stored by iGP Games. 

We use server management contractor companies as is necessary for the provision of our services to you. These contractor companies have access to your personal data so that the efficiency, security and integrity of the systems and databased behind the Game can be maintained. 

Your personal data may also be disclosed to sponsors to go on fictional cars within the Game. This will only be done with your prior consent in relation to each particular sponsor. 

To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. In certain instances, some entities also have their own policies regarding privacy and information protection, and these policies can be located in the areas of the Site or the Game where you are interacting with such third-party service providers. 

## V. DISPUTE RESOLUTION

A. You agree that should any dispute or claim arise out of, or relate to, this Policy ("Claim"), you will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the Claim directly with us. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for thirty (30) days after one party has provided written notice of the Claim to the other party, all parties shall join in mediation services in England with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. 

B. iGP Games will send its notice to the address it has on file to the extent that you have provided additional contact information to iGP Games (e.g. by participating in a promotion, survey or contacting a customer services representative). Otherwise, iGP Games will send its notice to the email address associated with your Account. You will send your notice to iGP Games, Third Floor, 207 Regent Street, London, W1B 3HH. 

C. Please note that this informal resolution procedure does not suspend any statutory limitation periods applicable to the bringing of a Claim and it does not affect your rights outlined in section I.F of this Policy. 

## VI. AUTOMATED DECISION-MAKING AND PROFILING

A. We use automated decisions and profiling to offer discounts and certain products. 

B. In the event that we use personal data for the purposes of automated decision-making and those decisions have a legal (or similarly significant effect) on you, you have the right to challenge to such decisions under GDPR, requesting human intervention, expressing their own point of view, and obtaining an explanation of the decision from us. 

C. The right described in section VI.C does not apply in the following circumstances: 

  1. the decision is necessary for the entry into, or performance of, a contract between the you and us; 
  2. the decision is authorised by law; or 
  3. you have given you explicit consent. 

D. Where we use your personal data for profiling purposes, the following shall apply: 

  1. Clear information explaining the profiling will be provided, including its significance and the likely consequences; 
  2. Appropriate mathematical or statistical procedures will be used; 
  3. Technical and organisational measures necessary to minimise the risk of errors and to enable such errors to be easily corrected shall be implemented; and 
  4. All personal data processed for profiling purposes shall be secured in order to prevent discriminatory effects arising out of profiling. 

## VII. ACCOUNT DEACTIVATION AND DELETION

If you want to stop using your account you may deactivate or delete it. When you deactivate and account, no user will be able to see your manager profile but it will not be deleted and can be reactivated. When you delete an account it is permanently deleted from the Game and cannot be recovered. To request deactivation or deletion of your account, contact the [Support Team](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com). 

After you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable to the extent it has been shared with others or was copied or stored by other users. However, if you delete your account, your name will no longer be associated with that information on the Game. For example, if you post something to another user's profile and then you delete your account, that post may remain, but be attributed to another name, such as "Unknown". 

Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies but will not be available to any second or third-party organisations. We may retain your Account information for a reasonable period of time afterwards for the purposes for internal account management and fraud prevention activities. 

## VIII. OTHER TERMS

Unless stated otherwise, this Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. If we make changes to this Policy we will notify you by publication here. If the changes are material, we will provide you additional, prominent notice as appropriate under the circumstances. 

Consent to Collection and Processing in the United Kingdom. By using the Game or Site in situations where we process your personal data on the basis of consent you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United Kingdom. ~~~~

## IX. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

###  A. Contacting Us 

If you have any concerns or queries about this Policy, our practices regarding your personal information related to the Site or Game, or any other matter relating to our service, please contact the [Support Team](mailto:contact@igpmanager.com) or write to iGP Games Limited, Third Floor, 207 Regent Street, London, W1B 3HH. 

###  B. Updates and Changes 

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms. 

BY USING THE SITE AND/OR THE GAME, YOU SIGNIFY THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SITE OR THE GAME. 

###  C. Additional Policies 

There are additional iGP Games legal policies that govern your use of the Site and the Game. Please take time to review and familiarise yourself with both the Terms of Service and the EULA.
